A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Photographic Files, RG 4 FA1288
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographic Files, Accession 2016:070, 1920-2006; 1
  - Washington DC Humphrey Workshop '90s, 1990s (Box 47, Folder 396)
  - Hungarian Refugee Student Program (Box 47, Folder 397)
  - Honorary Board Members, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 398)
  - Humphrey Fellowship (Box 47, Folder 399)
  - Hubert Humphrey Dinner, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 400-401)
  - Humphrey Minnesota Workshop, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 402)
  - HHH Fellowships/Misc. (Box 48, Folder 403)
  - Hill and Knowlton Fellowship (Box 48, Folder 404)
  - Holland Award Ceremony, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 405)
  - Holland, Kenneth (Box 49, Folder 406-407)
  - Hong Kong and Indonesia, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 408)
  - Hong Kong Students 1980s (Box 49, Folder 409)
  - GE Assembly, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 410)
  - GE Debriefing Mexico, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 411)
  - Ghana, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 412)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 49, Folder 413)
  - Guyer, David L. (Box 49, Folder 414)
  - HHH Fellowships, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 415)
  - HHH Fellowships, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 416)
  - HHH Fellowships, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 417)
  - HHH Fellowships Miscellaneous 1980s (Box 50, Folder 418)
  - Global Gala, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 419)
  - 2nd Global Gala, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 420)
  - Gala, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 421-422)
  - Fulbright LA, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Fulbright National Screening Committee, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 424)
  - Fulbright National Screening Committee, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 425)
  - Fulbright Screening Committee, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 426)
  - Fulbright Screening Committee, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 427)
  - Fulbright Painting Show, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 428)
  - Fulbright, J. William (Box 51, Folder 429)
  - Winter Party (II), 1982 (Box 51, Folder 430-431)
  - Winter Party (II), 1982 (Box 52, Folder 432-434)
  - Winter Party, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 435-437)
  - Winter Party, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 438-439)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 440)
  - Winter Party (Box 53, Folder 441)
  - Winter Party, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 442)
  - Winter Party, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 443-444)
  - Winter Party, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 445)
  - Winter Party, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 446-447)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 448)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 449)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 450)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 451)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 452)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 453)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 454)
  - L. Woods documents, 1951-1958 (Box 56, Folder 455)
  - L. Woods 1959-1960s (Box 56, Folder 456-457)
  - L. Woods Collection, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 458)
  - Woods, Louise (Box 56, Folder 459-460)
  - Woods, Louise (Box 57, Folder 461)
  - Wolfe, Glenn G. (Box 57, Folder 462)
  - "Young Americans" Associates Event, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 463)
  - Zacanas, Augustino (Box 57, Folder 464)
  - Students at Columbia Spring, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 465)
  - Students 1970s (Box 57, Folder 466)
  - Salsburg Summer School (Box 57, Folder 467)
  - San Diego Crossroads, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 468)
  - Sandriser Students, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 469-471)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company Dinner in Chicago, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 472)
  - Sesame Street (Box 58, Folder 473)
  - Soviet Ministers' Trip to U.S. (Box 58, Folder 474)
  - Stanford University (Box 58, Folder 475)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 58, Folder 476)
  - Student Party, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 477)
  - Student Party, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 478)
  - Student Halloween Party, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 479)
  - Student Conference on International Business, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 480)
  - Students 1980s (Box 59, Folder 481)
  - Study Abroad Conference in Hong Kong, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 482-484)
  - Swarthmore College (Box 60, Folder 485)
  - Switzerland, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 486)
  - Tanzania (Box 60, Folder 487)
  - Thai Luncheon, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 488-489)
  - Thurston, John L. (Box 60, Folder 490)
  - TOYL Seminar, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 491)
  - Traveling Seminar, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 492)
  - Tri-Lateral Journalists, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 493)
  - Trustee Luncheon, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 494)
  - Tufts University (Box 60, Folder 495)
  - Tutu, Desmond (Box 60, Folder 496)
  - UAR-USA Educational Exchange Commission Orientation Program, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 497)
  - Uganda Electoral Assistance Project, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 498)
  - University of Cambridge - Trinity College Library (Box 61, Folder 499)
  - University of Costa Rica (Box 61, Folder 500)
  - University of Hawaii (Box 61, Folder 501)
  - University of Illinois (Box 61, Folder 502)
  - University of Miami (Box 61, Folder 503)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 61, Folder 504)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 61, Folder 505)
  - University of Vermont (Box 61, Folder 506)
  - University of Vienna (Box 61, Folder 507)
  - Marconi International Fellowship, 1996-1998 (Box 61, Folder 508)
  - Braga Memorial (Box 61, Folder 509)
  - Leroy Keith, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 510)
  - Paul Simon, 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 511)
  - Martin Meyerson, 1994-2006 (Box 62, Folder 512)
  - Sylvia Ortega, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 513)
  - Daniel P. Moynihan, May 12, 1986, HL, 1986 May 12 (Box 62, Folder 514)
  - IIE Development Committee, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 515)
  - Roderick McManigal, 1994-1998 (Box 62, Folder 516)
  - Podium Book Index (Box 62, Folder 517)
  - Program - Luncheon Honoring Ted Stevens and John Kerry, 2001 April 2-5 (Box 62, Folder 518)
  - James H. Evans, 1989-1998 (Box 62, Folder 519)
  - Philippe Dunoyer, 1993-1995 (Box 62, Folder 520)
  - Richard Riley Connaroe, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 521)
  - IIE 75th Anniversary, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 522)
  - IIE - Background Information (Box 63, Folder 523-524)
  - Jack Nash, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 525)
  - Hon. Henry H. Fowler, 1993-1997 (Box 63, Folder 526)
  - Shigekuni Kawamura, 1993-1999 (Box 63, Folder 527)
  - Bruce W. Hulbert, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 528)
  - Judy Harrison, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 529)
  - Sheila Hehmeyer, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 530)
  - Alumni Profiles - Faces of IIE (Box 63, Folder 531)
  - Distinguished American and Foreign IIE Alumni (students), Lecturers, Debaters and Specialists, 1961 June 23 (Box 63, Folder 532)
  - The Diamond Ball, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 533)
  - Hungarian Refugee Students and United States Colleges and Universities, 1956-1958 (Box 64, Folder 534)
  - 1976 Winter Party Committee (Box 64, Folder 535)
  - Photos Used for 1980 Winter Party Program (Box 64, Folder 536)
  - 1982 Winter Party Photos - Cunningham (Box 64, Folder 537)
  - Photos - 1983 Committee Winter Party Meeting, 1982 October 28 (Box 64, Folder 538)
  - Telephone Logs, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 539)
  - Diaries, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 540)
- Photographic Files, Accession 2017:006, 1961-1998; 2
  - CIVITAS, 1997 April (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1988 Annual Report Historic Photos (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1961-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fulbright Dinner Photos, Jeanne Trudeau, 1986 December 17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fulbright Dinner, Irving Newman, 1986 December 17 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - City at Peace (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 3616 Kenneth Holland Event, 1998 (Box 4a, Folder 1-4)
  - Global DT 2 Sesame Street Egyptians (Box 4a, Folder 5)
  - Increasing Females Participation Conference, 1995 (Box 4b, Folder 1)
  - Trustee Dinner - Mostly Fulbrights, 1997 (Box 4b, Folder 2-3)
  - Fulbright Leadership Dinner (Box 4b, Folder 4)
  - Alhambra (for Vanesa Palmer), 1992 (Box 4b, Folder 5)
  - 35mm Color Slides, Various Events (Box 4c, Folder 1)
  - Bill Ulfelder Fulbright to Panama, 1990-1991 (Box 4c, Folder 2)
  - Untitled 35mm Slides, 1986 (Box 4c, Folder 3)
  - Russian Students, 1987 (Box 4c, Folder 4)
  - World Forum - Fulbright Alumni, 1992 June 5 (Box 4c, Folder 5)
  - University Fairs (Box 4c, Folder 6)
  - FMF Photos (Box 4c, Folder 7)
  - K. Holland Awards for Annual Report 1996 (Box 4c, Folder 8)
  - Solar Water Pumping Course, Mexico, 1994 (Box 4c, Folder 9)
  - United Nations Plaza, 1992 (Box 4c, Folder 10)
  - Prints, transparencies, and negatives marked for publication (Box 4d, Folder 1-2)
  - Headshots and Group shots (Box 4d, Folder 3)
  - Progressive Architecture, 1965 February (Box 4d, Folder 4)
  - Photos marked for publication (Box 4d, Folder 5)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
    Scope and Contents
    Digital material within
  - Photos Inserted Into Online Database (Box 4d, Folder 6)
  - Untitled Event Photos (Box 4d, Folder 7)
  - Signing of IIE agreement with Fulbright and Conacyt (Box 4e, Folder 1)
  - Negatives Sheet #1-2 (Box 4e, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 4e, Folder 3)
  - Guangdong American Study Information Center (Box 4e, Folder 4)
  - Richard M. Krasno, 1987 (Box 4e, Folder 5)
  - Mary Packard-Winkler, 1996 (Box 4e, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets (Box 4e, Folder 7)
  - Negatives, Untitled (Box 4e, Folder 8-11)
  - Gubenko Reception, 1990 (Box 4e, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (Box 4e, Folder 13)
  - 13242-1 thru 4 Negatives (Box 4e, Folder 14)
  - Jaime Abad of Panama (Box 4e, Folder 15)
  - South Africa Photos and Negatives, Bart Rousseue - Also Comm. Staff, 1988 November (Box 4e, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Annual Report Photos, 1989-1991 (Box 4e, Folder 17)
  - IIE History (Box 4e, Folder 18)
  - South Africa - Contacts and Negatives - Sheila McLean Summer '88, 1988 (Box 4e, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 4e, Folder 20)